smartassistant.com 2017-06-06

# Legal Information | SMARTASSISTANT

Copyrights 

The copyright of the materials published on this web page remains the property of the author. It is not permitted to copy or use any graphics or texts in either electronic or printed publications without the written consent of the author. We accept no responsibility for the content of linked web pages, as we have no influence over the content of these links.

Imprint 

Company name: Smart Information Systems GmbH  
Company type: Limited Liability Company  
Commercial register number: FN 281510k  
Value added tax identification number (VAT ID): ATU62847619  
Court of registry: Vienna Commercial Court  
Member of The Austrian Federal Economic Chamber

Terms of Service 

SMARTASSISTANT Professional Services Terms and Conditions

SMARTASSISTANT Software License Agreement

## Privacy Policy

This Application collects some Personal Data from its Users.

**Data Controller and Owner**

Smart Information Systems GmbH  
Bayerngasse 3/5  
AT-1030 Vienna

If you have any questions or concerns about data protection, you are welcome to contact us by email at this address: [office@smartassistant.com](mailto:office@smartassistant.com)

**Types of Data collected**

Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookie, Usage Data, First Name, Last Name, Profession, Address, Country and Email.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this privacy policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Data collection.  
The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.  
Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.

The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

## Mode and place of processing the Data

### Method of processing

The Data Controller processes the Data of Users in proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification or unauthorized destruction of the Data.  
The Data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated. In addition to the Data Controller, in some cases, the Data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge, involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) appointed, if necessary, as Data Processors by the Owner. The updated list of these parties may be requested from the Data Controller at any time.

### Place

The Data is processed at the Data Controller's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved with the processing are located. For further information, please contact the Data Controller.

### Conservation Time

The Data is kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request the Data Controller for their suspension or removal.

The use of the collected Data

The Data concerning the User is collected to allow the Application to provide its services, as well as for the following purposes: Analytics and Contacting the User.

The Personal Data used for each purpose is outlined in the specific sections of this document.

Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data

Personal Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  * ### Analytics

The services contained in this section enable the Owner to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

#### GOOGLE ADWORDS CONVERSION TRACKING (GOOGLE)

Google AdWords conversion tracking is an analytics service provided by Google, Inc. that connects data from the Google AdWords advertising network with actions performed on this Application.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### GOOGLE ANALYTICS (GOOGLE)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.  
Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

#### BURDA DIREKT SERVICES

We use products of Burda Direkt Services ([www.burdadirektservices.de](http://www.burdadirektservices.de/)) for marketing and optimization purposes. These products collect and process your personal data and use it to create usage profiles under a pseudonym. These usage profiles are fully anonymized where possible and appropriate. We and Burda Direkt Services employ cookies and/or Web beacons (also known as tracking pixels) on this Web site. We transfer the data we collect about you, which may also include personal data, to Burda Direkt Services or Burda Direkt Services gathers this data directly. Burda Direkt Services is entitled to use information that you leave behind by visiting our Web sites to create anonymized usage profiles. The data collected shall not be used to personally identify visitors to this Web site without the express permission of the party affected and shall not be merged with personal data about the bearer of the pseudonym. Any IP addresses recorded are anonymized immediately by deleting the last number block. Permission to collect and store data in the future may be revoked at any time.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Germany – [Opt Out](http://stats.vertriebsassistent.de/track/cookie_mgr.php?mode=dont_track_ask&websitesel=868ada5646ec6947&lang=de)

  * ### Contacting the User

#### CONTACT FORM (THIS APPLICATION)

By filling in the contact form with their Data, the Users authorizes this Application to use these details to reply to requests for information, quotes or any other kind of request as indicated by the form’s header.

Personal Data collected: Address, Country, Email, First Name, Last Name, Profession and Various types of Data.

#### MAILING LIST OR NEWSLETTER (THIS APPLICATION)

By registering to the mailing list or to the newsletter, the User’s email address will be added to the contact list of those who may receive email messages containing information of commercial or promotional nature concerning this Application. Your email address might also be added to this list as a result of signing up to this Application or after performing a purchase.

Personal Data collected: Email, First Name and Last Name.

  * ### Interaction with live chat platforms

These services allow Users to interact with third party live chat platforms directly from the pages of this Application, for contacting and being contacted by this Application support service.  
If one of these services is installed, it may collect browsing and usage data in the pages where it is installed, even if the Users do not actively use the service. Moreover, live chat conversations may be logged.

#### ZOPIM WIDGET (ZOPIM TECHNOLOGIES PTE LTD)

The Zopim Widget is a service for interacting with the Zopim live chat platform provided by Zopim Technologies Pte Ltd.

Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.

Place of processing: Singapore – [Privacy Policy](https://www.zopim.com/privacy)

Additional information about Data collection and processing

### Legal Action

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services.

### Additional Information about User's Personal Data

In addition to the information in this privacy policy, this Application may provide the User with contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data.

### System Logs and Maintenance

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

### Information not contained in this policy

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time at its contact information.

### The rights of Users

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out above.

This Application does not support “do not track” requests.  
To understand if any of the third party services it uses honor the “do not track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request the Data Controller to erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

Last update: August 20, 2015
